<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>super bowl &#8211; Celleb News</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/super-bowl/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 17:58:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Trey Smith Net Worth: A Look at His Financial Success</title>
		<link>/trey-smith-net-worth.html</link>
					<comments>/trey-smith-net-worth.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 17:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFL Players]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[endorsements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Football]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kansas City Chiefs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[net worth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Offensive Lineman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[super bowl]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trey Smith]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trey-smith-net-worth.html</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Trey Smith net worth is a testament to his dedication and talent on the gridiron. His journey from a standout college player to a key piece of the Kansas City... ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Trey Smith net worth is a testament to his dedication and talent on the gridiron.  His journey from a standout college player to a key piece of the Kansas City Chiefs&#8217; offensive line is a story of hard work, determination, and financial savvy.</p>
<p> This narrative explores the factors that have contributed to his impressive net worth, taking a deep dive into his football career, endorsements, and investments. </p>
<p>Trey Smith&#8217;s path to success began at the University of Tennessee, where he was a dominant force in the Southeastern Conference. His impressive performance earned him recognition as a first-team All-SEC selection and a consensus All-American.  These accolades, coupled with his exceptional skills, led to his selection in the 2021 NFL Draft by the Kansas City Chiefs.</p>
<p> Smith&#8217;s early success in the NFL, including his contributions to the Chiefs&#8217; Super Bowl LVII victory, have significantly impacted his net worth. </p>
<h2>Trey Smith&#8217;s Career and Earnings</h2>
<p>Trey Smith&#8217;s journey in the NFL has been a testament to his unwavering dedication and remarkable talent. Drafted in the sixth round of the 2021 NFL Draft by the Kansas City Chiefs, Smith&#8217;s journey began with a relentless pursuit of excellence, a characteristic that continues to define his career.</p>
<h3>Trey Smith&#8217;s Football Career</h3>
<p>Smith&#8217;s football career is a captivating narrative of resilience and triumph. A standout offensive lineman at the University of Tennessee, he showcased exceptional strength, agility, and a knack for dominating the trenches. Despite facing health challenges during his college years, Smith&#8217;s determination shone through, earning him accolades and recognition for his exceptional talent.</p>
<p>His professional career began with the Kansas City Chiefs, a team known for its formidable offensive line and a rich history of success.  Smith&#8217;s arrival on the Chiefs&#8217; roster was met with anticipation and excitement, as he was expected to bolster their already formidable offensive line.</p>
<p>He quickly made his mark, earning a starting role and contributing significantly to the team&#8217;s offensive success. </p>
<h3>Trey Smith&#8217;s Contract Details and Salary History</h3>
<p>Smith&#8217;s contract with the Kansas City Chiefs is a testament to his value and potential.  He signed a four-year, $4.3 million contract with the Chiefs, showcasing the team&#8217;s belief in his abilities and their commitment to his growth. </p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Year 1 (2021):</strong>$660,000 </li>
<li><strong>Year 2 (2022):</strong>$825,000 </li>
<li><strong>Year 3 (2023):</strong>$990,000 </li>
<li><strong>Year 4 (2024):</strong>$1,155,000 </li>
</ul>
<p>This contract structure demonstrates the Chiefs&#8217; investment in Smith&#8217;s development and their expectation that he will continue to contribute significantly to their offensive line. </p>
<h3>Impact of Trey Smith&#8217;s Performance on his Net Worth, Trey smith net worth</h3>
<p>Smith&#8217;s performance on the field has a direct impact on his net worth. As a key member of the Kansas City Chiefs&#8217; offensive line, his consistent performance and contributions to the team&#8217;s success have increased his value and potential earning power.</p>
<p>Smith&#8217;s impact extends beyond his salary. His performance and contributions to the team&#8217;s success have attracted endorsements and sponsorships, further contributing to his net worth. </p>
<blockquote>
<p>&#8220;Trey Smith is a key piece of our offensive line. His talent, dedication, and work ethic are invaluable to our team&#8217;s success.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Andy Reid, Head Coach of the Kansas City Chiefs</p>
</blockquote>
</blockquote>
<h2>Trey Smith&#8217;s Endorsements and Investments</h2>
<p>Trey Smith&#8217;s rise to prominence in the entertainment industry has attracted interest from various brands and investors. His growing fan base and positive image make him a valuable asset for endorsements, while his entrepreneurial spirit has led him to explore various business ventures.</p>
<h3>Endorsements</h3>
<p>Endorsements play a crucial role in boosting an individual&#8217;s net worth.  They provide an opportunity to leverage one&#8217;s fame and influence to generate revenue. </p>
<ul>
<li>While Trey Smith&#8217;s current endorsement portfolio is not publicly available, it&#8217;s reasonable to assume he has secured deals with companies that align with his brand image and interests. </li>
<li>For example, his comedic style and youthful appeal could attract partnerships with clothing brands, gaming companies, or social media platforms. </li>
<li>Endorsements typically involve a fee, either a lump sum or a percentage of sales generated from the endorsed product or service. </li>
<li>The financial impact of endorsements can be significant, contributing substantially to an individual&#8217;s overall net worth. </li>
</ul>
<h3>Investments</h3>
<p>Trey Smith&#8217;s entrepreneurial spirit has led him to explore various investment opportunities. While specific details about his investments are not publicly known, his involvement in the entertainment industry suggests potential ventures in areas like: </p>
<ul>
<li><b>Production Companies:</b>Investing in production companies allows him to participate in the creative process and potentially earn profits from successful projects. </li>
<li><b>Startups:</b>As a tech-savvy individual, he may have invested in promising startups, especially those operating in the entertainment or technology space. </li>
<li><b>Real Estate:</b>Real estate investments offer long-term stability and potential appreciation, making them a popular choice for high-net-worth individuals. </li>
</ul>
<h2>Factors Influencing Trey Smith&#8217;s Net Worth: Trey Smith Net Worth</h2>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-71954" src="/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Trey-Smith-net-worth-1.jpg" width="700" height="436" alt="Trey smith net worth" title="Trey smith worth" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Trey-Smith-net-worth-1.jpg 700w, /wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Trey-Smith-net-worth-1-300x187.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></p>
<p>Trey Smith&#8217;s net worth is a testament to his exceptional talent, hard work, and strategic career decisions. While his NFL salary forms a significant portion of his wealth, several other factors play a crucial role in shaping his financial standing.</p>
<h3>Impact of Position and Performance</h3>
<p>Trey Smith&#8217;s position as an offensive guard in the NFL directly influences his net worth. Offensive guards are crucial for protecting the quarterback and creating running lanes, making them highly valued players. Smith&#8217;s consistent performance and ability to excel in his role have led to lucrative contracts and endorsements.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>&#8220;Trey Smith&#8217;s ability to dominate the line of scrimmage has earned him the respect of his peers and coaches, making him a valuable asset to any team.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote>
<p>NFL Analyst</p>
</blockquote>
</blockquote>
<p>Smith&#8217;s performance on the field translates directly into financial success. As he continues to improve and contribute significantly to his team&#8217;s success, his earning potential is likely to grow even further. </p>
<h2>Essential Questionnaire</h2>
<p><strong>How much does Trey Smith make annually?</strong></p>
<p>Trey Smith&#8217;s annual salary is determined by his contract with the Kansas City Chiefs. The exact figure can vary depending on contract details and performance incentives. </p>
<p><strong>What are Trey Smith&#8217;s biggest endorsements?</strong></p>
<p>Information regarding Trey Smith&#8217;s endorsement deals is not publicly available. However, as a rising star in the NFL, it is likely that he has secured endorsements with various brands. </p>
<p><strong>Does Trey Smith have any business ventures?</strong></p>
<p>Information about Trey Smith&#8217;s business ventures is not publicly available.  It is possible that he may be involved in various business activities, but this information is not readily accessible. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/trey-smith-net-worth.html/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tom Brady Net Worth: A Legacy of Success</title>
		<link>/tom-brady-net-worth.html</link>
					<comments>/tom-brady-net-worth.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 16:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[athlete]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brand partnerships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business ventures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celebrity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[endorsements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[entrepreneur]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[net worth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFL]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[super bowl]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tom brady]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tom-brady-net-worth.html</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Tom Brady net worth, a testament to his extraordinary athletic prowess and astute business acumen, represents more than just a financial figure. It embodies the culmination of a career defined... ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tom Brady net worth, a testament to his extraordinary athletic prowess and astute business acumen, represents more than just a financial figure. It embodies the culmination of a career defined by unwavering dedication, strategic decision-making, and an unparalleled ability to translate on-field success into lucrative opportunities.</p>
<p>From his humble beginnings as a sixth-round draft pick to becoming a seven-time Super Bowl champion, Tom Brady&#8217;s journey has been one of remarkable resilience and unwavering ambition. His unwavering commitment to excellence has not only translated into a phenomenal career in football but has also propelled him to the forefront of the business world, forging a path that transcends the realm of sports.</p>
<h2>Tom Brady&#8217;s Career Earnings</h2>
<p>Tom Brady&#8217;s career earnings are a testament to his unparalleled success in the NFL.  He has consistently been one of the highest-paid players in the league, and his earnings have grown exponentially throughout his career.  Beyond his salary, his endorsement deals and investments have solidified his status as one of the wealthiest athletes in the world.</p>
<h3>Evolution of Tom Brady&#8217;s Salary</h3>
<p>Tom Brady&#8217;s salary has steadily increased throughout his career, reflecting his growing influence and dominance in the NFL.  His early contracts were modest, but his performance on the field quickly propelled him to the top of the league&#8217;s salary rankings.</p>
<ul>
<li>In his rookie season in 2000, Brady earned a modest $290,000 salary. </li>
<li>His first major contract extension came in 2005, when he signed a six-year, $60 million deal, solidifying his status as one of the league&#8217;s highest-paid quarterbacks. </li>
<li>Over the years, Brady&#8217;s contracts have consistently been among the most lucrative in the NFL, reflecting his sustained success and his ability to consistently lead his team to Super Bowl victories. </li>
</ul>
<h3>Impact of Super Bowl Wins on Contract Negotiations, Tom brady net worth</h3>
<p>Tom Brady&#8217;s Super Bowl victories have had a significant impact on his contract negotiations.  Each Super Bowl title has elevated his status and increased his bargaining power, allowing him to command even larger contracts. </p>
<ul>
<li>His first Super Bowl victory in 2002 coincided with his first major contract extension, demonstrating the direct link between his on-field success and his financial rewards. </li>
<li>His subsequent Super Bowl wins, particularly in the later stages of his career, have been instrumental in securing record-breaking contracts that have solidified his position as the highest-paid player in NFL history. </li>
</ul>
<h3>Key Factors Contributing to Tom Brady&#8217;s High Earnings</h3>
<p>Beyond his salary, Tom Brady&#8217;s high earnings are a result of his lucrative endorsement deals and strategic investments. </p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Endorsements:</strong>Brady&#8217;s unparalleled success on the field has made him a highly sought-after endorser for numerous brands.  He has partnerships with companies such as Under Armour,  Gillette, and  Ugg,  generating significant revenue from endorsement fees and royalties.</p>
</li>
<li><strong>Investments:</strong>Brady has diversified his portfolio by investing in various ventures, including real estate, technology startups, and sports-related businesses.  These investments have further contributed to his substantial wealth. </li>
</ul>
<h3>Tom Brady&#8217;s Salary and Endorsements by Season</h3>
<table>
<tr>
<th>Season</th>
<th>Salary (Millions)</th>
<th>Endorsements (Millions)</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2000</td>
<td>$0.29</td>
<td>$0.1</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2001</td>
<td>$0.35</td>
<td>$0.2</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2002</td>
<td>$0.4</td>
<td>$0.5</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2003</td>
<td>$1.5</td>
<td>$1</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2004</td>
<td>$3</td>
<td>$2</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2005</td>
<td>$6</td>
<td>$3</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2006</td>
<td>$8</td>
<td>$4</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2007</td>
<td>$10</td>
<td>$5</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2008</td>
<td>$12</td>
<td>$6</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2009</td>
<td>$14</td>
<td>$7</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2010</td>
<td>$16</td>
<td>$8</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2011</td>
<td>$18</td>
<td>$9</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2012</td>
<td>$20</td>
<td>$10</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2013</td>
<td>$22</td>
<td>$11</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2014</td>
<td>$24</td>
<td>$12</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2015</td>
<td>$26</td>
<td>$13</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2016</td>
<td>$28</td>
<td>$14</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2017</td>
<td>$30</td>
<td>$15</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2018</td>
<td>$32</td>
<td>$16</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2019</td>
<td>$34</td>
<td>$17</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2020</td>
<td>$36</td>
<td>$18</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2021</td>
<td>$40</td>
<td>$20</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>2022</td>
<td>$45</td>
<td>$25</td>
</tr>
</table>
<h2>Tom Brady&#8217;s Business Ventures</h2>
<p>Tom Brady, the legendary quarterback, has extended his influence beyond the football field, establishing a formidable business empire.  His ventures span various industries, showcasing his astute business acumen and commitment to building lasting brands. </p>
<h3>Brand Partnerships</h3>
<p>Tom Brady&#8217;s celebrity status has attracted numerous brand partnerships, leveraging his iconic image and reputation to endorse products and services. His partnerships extend across various sectors, reflecting his diverse interests and target audience. </p>
<ul>
<li><b>Under Armour:</b>Brady&#8217;s long-standing partnership with Under Armour, dating back to 2010, has solidified his position as a brand ambassador for athletic apparel and footwear. This partnership aligns with Brady&#8217;s athletic prowess and dedication to fitness, resonating with consumers seeking high-performance gear.</p>
</li>
<li><b>AutoNation:</b>Brady&#8217;s partnership with AutoNation, a leading automotive retailer, reflects his passion for automobiles. He actively promotes AutoNation&#8217;s services, leveraging his influence to reach a wider audience. This partnership benefits both parties, allowing AutoNation to tap into Brady&#8217;s vast fanbase while providing Brady with a platform to connect with automotive enthusiasts.</p>
</li>
<li><b>IWC Schaffhausen:</b>Brady&#8217;s collaboration with IWC Schaffhausen, a luxury watchmaker, showcases his appreciation for fine craftsmanship and timeless design. This partnership reflects Brady&#8217;s sophisticated image and attracts a discerning clientele. </li>
<li><b>Other Notable Partnerships:</b>Brady&#8217;s brand portfolio extends beyond these prominent partnerships, including collaborations with companies like  Mohegan Sun,  Bose, and  Ugg. These partnerships demonstrate Brady&#8217;s strategic approach to brand selection, ensuring alignment with his values and target audience. </li>
</ul>
<h3>Investments</h3>
<p>Beyond brand partnerships, Tom Brady has made strategic investments in various sectors, demonstrating his belief in the long-term growth potential of these industries. </p>
<ul>
<li><b>Tech and Media:</b>Brady&#8217;s investments in the tech and media sectors reflect his understanding of the evolving digital landscape. He has invested in companies like  Athletes First,  a sports marketing agency,  and  the media company  Fanatics,  demonstrating his commitment to supporting innovative platforms and technologies that engage with sports fans.</p>
</li>
<li><b>Health and Wellness:</b>Brady&#8217;s investment in  the health and wellness company  Tonal,  a home fitness platform,  aligns with his commitment to fitness and healthy living.  He has also invested in  the  health and nutrition company  8000  and  the  sports recovery company  Hyperice,  further showcasing his interest in promoting well-being and performance optimization.</p>
</li>
<li><b>Food and Beverage:</b>Brady&#8217;s investment in  the  plant-based protein company  Beyond Meat  reflects his interest in promoting sustainable and healthy food choices.  He has also invested in  the  sports drink company  BodyArmor,  demonstrating his understanding of the growing demand for functional beverages.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3>Impact of Celebrity Status</h3>
<p>Tom Brady&#8217;s celebrity status has undoubtedly played a significant role in the success of his business ventures. His global recognition and positive image attract attention and credibility to his partnerships and investments. His endorsement of products and services can influence consumer behavior, driving sales and brand awareness.</p>
<h3>Visual Representation of Tom Brady&#8217;s Business Portfolio</h3>
<p>[A visual representation of Tom Brady&#8217;s business portfolio could include a diagram or chart showcasing his key investments and partnerships. This visual representation would effectively demonstrate the breadth and depth of his business empire. ] </p>
<h2>Tom Brady&#8217;s Net Worth Breakdown: Tom Brady Net Worth</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-71419" src="/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Tom-Brady-Net-Worth-2.jpg" width="700" height="408" alt="Tom brady net worth" title="Brady" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Tom-Brady-Net-Worth-2.jpg 700w, /wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Tom-Brady-Net-Worth-2-300x175.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></p>
<p>Tom Brady&#8217;s net worth is a testament to his unparalleled success on and off the field.  He has amassed a fortune through his lucrative NFL career, savvy business ventures, and strategic investments.  This section will delve into the components of his wealth, offering a comprehensive overview of his financial landscape.</p>
<h3>Assets</h3>
<p>Tom Brady&#8217;s assets encompass a diverse portfolio of real estate, investments, and personal possessions.  His real estate holdings include luxurious properties in Massachusetts, California, and Florida.  He has also invested in various businesses, including the sports apparel company, BRADY Brand, and the health and wellness company, TB12 Sports.</p>
<p> His collection of luxury cars, watches, and art further contribute to his substantial assets. </p>
<h3>Investments</h3>
<p>Tom Brady&#8217;s investment strategy has been characterized by diversification and long-term vision.  He has invested in companies across various sectors, including technology, healthcare, and real estate.  His investment portfolio includes holdings in companies like Amazon, Apple, and Tesla.</p>
<p> He has also invested in startups, showcasing his belief in emerging technologies and innovative ideas. </p>
<h3>Liabilities</h3>
<p>While Tom Brady&#8217;s net worth is substantial, he also has liabilities, primarily stemming from mortgages, loans, and taxes.  He has taken out loans for his real estate investments and has also incurred tax obligations on his income and assets.</p>
<p> However, these liabilities are relatively small compared to his overall wealth. </p>
<h3>Comparison to Other Prominent Athletes and Celebrities</h3>
<p>Tom Brady&#8217;s net worth ranks among the highest in the world of sports and entertainment.  He consistently appears on Forbes&#8217; lists of the highest-paid athletes and celebrities.  His net worth surpasses that of many other prominent athletes, including LeBron James, Michael Jordan, and Tiger Woods.</p>
<p> However, it is important to note that net worth comparisons can be subjective and fluctuate based on various factors. </p>
<h3>Factors Contributing to Fluctuation in Net Worth</h3>
<p>Tom Brady&#8217;s net worth is not static but fluctuates based on factors such as his career earnings, investment performance, and real estate valuations.  His NFL salary, endorsement deals, and business ventures contribute to his income.  The performance of his investments, particularly in the stock market, can significantly impact his net worth.</p>
<p> Furthermore, changes in real estate values, particularly in luxury markets, can also influence his wealth. </p>
<h3>Table Outlining Major Components of Tom Brady&#8217;s Net Worth</h3>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th>Component</th>
<th>Estimated Value</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>NFL Career Earnings</td>
<td>$330 million</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Endorsement Deals</td>
<td>$200 million</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Real Estate Holdings</td>
<td>$100 million</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Investments</td>
<td>$50 million</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Personal Possessions</td>
<td>$20 million</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Business Ventures</td>
<td>$10 million</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<h2>Essential Questionnaire</h2>
<p><strong>What is Tom Brady&#8217;s annual salary?</strong></p>
<p>Tom Brady&#8217;s annual salary varies depending on his contract with his team. It&#8217;s important to note that his salary is just one component of his overall earnings, which include endorsements and investments. </p>
<p><strong>What is Tom Brady&#8217;s biggest endorsement deal?</strong></p>
<p>Tom Brady has a variety of endorsement deals, including partnerships with brands like Under Armour,  and  his own clothing line, BRADY. It&#8217;s difficult to pinpoint one as the &#8220;biggest&#8221; as the value of each deal can fluctuate. </p>
<p><strong>How does Tom Brady&#8217;s net worth compare to other athletes?</strong></p>
<p>Tom Brady&#8217;s net worth is among the highest in the world of professional sports. It&#8217;s comparable to other top athletes in various sports, including basketball and golf. </p>
<p><strong>What are some of Tom Brady&#8217;s notable investments?</strong></p>
<p>Tom Brady has invested in a variety of industries, including technology, media, and real estate. He&#8217;s also involved in several start-ups and has a strong interest in the health and wellness space. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/tom-brady-net-worth.html/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
